Oh
back in 2014 my gun control routine went
viral and the media couldn't get enough
Jim Jefferies throwing down truth I was
henceforth known as the gun control guy
so now with students across the nation
putting gun control back in the
spotlight the movements gonna need its
hero again America needs me it's time to
suit up and show these kids how it's
done
dry cleaners shrink everything I
headed south to San Diego and when I got
there the March was in full force now I
don't like being mobbed by fans but if
it helps out the students it'll be worth
it
I'm here with an impressive group of
young people I'm sure many of you are
here because you are influenced by my
twenty twelve stand-up routine on Bear
about gun control right my twenty twelve
Netflix special there so it's on YouTube
kids like into the bit where I go to the
safes very good when I go there safe you
bring guns to a drone fight that's on
the special as well
machine muskets loading a musket gives
you a lot of time to calm down who's the
Joker you recognize this jacket still
fits right these kids don't seem to
realize how lucky they are that I'm here
if you are star power isn't working I'll
just connect with them on their level
what is the quick quick quick thing what
is this guns are cray-cray I'm all right
what's it like being an 18 year old in
school these days we have kids at our
school that have guns in their locker
it's definitely changed in that aspect
you don't get the same education is um
is fingerings still thing
what a relief you know that some things
never change
and you know what else never changes for
decades adults have been sitting on
protest movements by saying they're just
a bunch of kids if you're too immature
to carry a firearm you're too immature
to make policy about firearms they're
children they're not old enough to have
the perspective that adults do what
makes you think that a bunch of kids can
actually make real change in this issue
I think this generation is just really
ambitious and determined we go to school
every day we live in these communities
that are infiltrated with gun violence
and we're tired of it once we're all old
enough to vote we're gonna make change
and we're not just gonna sit around and
do nothing while people are dying don't
you a little bit you know immature and
emotional to speak about this complex
issue you're not in high school what's
your qualification you get distracted
very easy if they play you dissing your
donkey kong's you kids
as a school teacher how do you feel
about being armed I would absolutely
quit my job before I ever had to have a
weapon on me in the classroom after the
third or fourth school shooting you'll
be good at it
you could write they could be shooting
the hallway and you can get you and the
other teachers who had guns would know
that you're the good person with a gun
and they wouldn't shoot you there
wouldn't be more people shooting that
would be ridiculous yeah no I'm a
serious journalist
so I also gave the counter protesters
their chance to speak and one of them
weighed in with all of this his deep
state false flag operations you think
you think what happened to these schools
we think what happened in Sandy Hook was
a false flag crisis actors they were
holding the FEMA drill there at the time
Boston Marathon Sandy Hook 9/11 all deep
state false flag operations
in order to create a police state to
take our guns away we're not crazy they
are they're Psychopaths run in the world
looks like pop eyes looked unwell in
retirement but pop eyes not alone
pushing crisis acta conspiracy theories
how do I know that you're an actual
student and not across the sector I'm
broke how do I know that you're not
actually 35 year old women and your
crisis actors you could be like from 21
Jump Street and just infiltrating the
whole thing like you saw you 16 you
could be 15 well I'll see the story has
changed I don't even know what that
means I'm a little simple task as a
viewer as old as you say you are
I'm assume you've never heard of the
sitcom cheers Cheers
yeah cheers crisis actor when I say what
you're talking about Willis what does
that mean that means you're talking to
man named Willis and he's not me I'm
getting the full I pity the fool you
pity the fool stop you a jibba jabba
jibber jabber Inc is uneducated do you
feel like these interviews jump the
shock I would hope not I have a shark
phobia so they're not cross the sector's
they're matura they're passionate
in fact most kids probably think the
adults are the ones who are too immature
to deal with gun control after all we've
been talking about this issue for
literally their entire lives and what
have we accomplished maybe it's time to
just take a step back and listen how
many shootings there have to be how many
live need to be live what stops a bad
guy with the gun is not a good guy with
a gun it is hundreds of thousands of
students millions of people across these
United States marching through the
streets together
[Applause]
we are the change if you listen real
close you can hear the people in power
shaking on you there was only one thing
left to do
look you're a really impressive young
man I'm ready to pass the baton on to
the next generation I think you can now
wear the jacket oh it's hot I know
just try it on
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]